<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cinema</string>
    <string name="start">   Now you can log in, Discover movies and buy tickets to the movie you like!</string>
    <string name="Unfortunate_Events">  After their parents die in a mysterious fire, the Baudelaire orphans—Violet, Klaus, and Sunny—are sent to live with their evil relative, Count Olaf. He is only after their inheritance and will do anything to get it. As they move from one eccentric guardian to another, they must outsmart Olaf’s disguises and sinister schemes while uncovering secrets about their family\'s past. </string>
    <string name="Alone">   The story follows Pim, a woman who returns to Thailand after her mother\'s illness. However, she starts experiencing eerie supernatural occurrences. As she reconnects with her past, she is haunted by the spirit of her conjoined twin sister, Ploy, who died after they were surgically separated.</string>
    <string name="Alice_In_WonderLnad"> Alice, a curious young girl, follows a mysterious white rabbit down a rabbit hole and enters the whimsical world of Wonderland. There, she encounters bizarre creatures like the Cheshire Cat, the Mad Hatter, and the Queen of Hearts. As she navigates this dreamlike land, Alice must find her courage, solve riddles, and challenge the Queen\'s tyrannical rule to discover her own destiny.</string>
    <string name="The_nun"> In 1952, a young nun in a Romanian abbey mysteriously takes her own life. The Vatican sends Father Burke, a priest with a haunted past, and Sister Irene, a novitiate with visions, to investigate. As they uncover dark secrets, they realize the abbey is haunted by Valak, a demonic nun.</string>
    <string name="Paddington">  A young Peruvian bear with a love for marmalade travels to London in search of a new home. Lost and alone at Paddington Station, he is taken in by the kind-hearted Brown family. As he tries to adjust to city life, his clumsy nature leads to hilarious misadventures. But danger lurks when a sinister taxidermist wants to capture him for a museum! With the help of his new family, Paddington proves that kindness and a warm heart can make anyone feel at home. </string>
    <string name="night_house"> After her husband\'s unexpected suicide, Beth is left alone in their isolated lakeside house. Struggling with grief, she begins experiencing disturbing visions—strange noises, eerie shadows, and a mirror version of her home appearing at night. As she digs deeper, she uncovers dark secrets about her husband\'s double life and a terrifying supernatural presence lurking in the house. Reality and nightmare blur as Beth races to uncover the truth before it consumes her</string>
    <string name="The_Fox_And_The_Hound">   A young fox named Tod and a hound puppy named Copper become best friends despite being natural enemies. As they grow older, their friendship is tested when Copper is trained to be a hunting dog, and Tod is seen as prey. Fate forces them to stand on opposite sides, leading to an emotional journey of friendship, loyalty, and survival. In the end, despite their differences, they share a silent understanding—a bittersweet farewell to the friendship they once had</string>
    <string name="it">   In the summer of 1989, a group of bullied kids band together to destroy a shape-shifting monster, which disguises itself as a clown and preys on the children of Derry, their small Maine town</string>
    <string name="The_Cat_in_the_Hat">  Two bored kids are home alone on a rainy day when The Cat in the Hat, a mischievous talking cat, shows up. With his crazy tricks and wild adventures, he turns their house upside down, causing chaos before fixing everything just in time! </string>
    <string name="The_Last_Voyage">   A chilling horror film based on a chapter from Bram Stoker\'s Dracula. The crew of the Demeter unknowingly transports Dracula in a coffin, only to be hunted one by one as the ship sails towards England. Trapped at sea, they fight for survival against the legendary vampire, but few live to tell the tale.</string>
    <string name="The_adventures_of_tintin">  Young journalist Tintin, along with his loyal dog Snowy, uncovers a centuries-old mystery after finding a model ship linked to the legendary Unicorn. Teaming up with the unpredictable Captain Haddock, they embark on a globe-trotting adventure to locate hidden treasure before the sinister Ivan Sakharine can claim it. Clues, danger, and thrilling chases lead them to an epic discovery! </string>
    <string name="lilo_stitch">  Lilo and Stitch’ is the story of a lonely Hawaiian girl and the fugitive alien who helps to mend her broken family.</string>
    <string name="histoire">Tandis qu’il pédale dans les rues de Paris pour livrer des repas, Souleymane répète son histoire. Dans deux jours, il doit passer son entretien de demande d’asile, le sésame pour obtenir des papiers. Mais Souleymane n’est pas prêt.</string>
    <string name="the_fall_guy">  C\'est l\'histoire d\'un cascadeur, et comme tous les cascadeurs, c\'est un homme qui est lancé d\'explosions en explosions, qui se fait tirer dessus, cabosser, écraser, passer par les fenêtres et qui tombe irrémédiablement et toujours, de plus en plus haut… le tout pour le plus grand plaisir du public. C\'est tout juste après un accident qui a failli mettre fin à sa carrière, que cet anonyme et pourtant véritable héros des plateaux de tournage, va devoir retrouver une star de cinéma portée disparue, déjouer un complot et tenter de reconquérir la femme de sa vie tout en assurant chaque jour ses cascades sur les plateaux. Que pourrait-il bien lui arriver de pire ?</string>
    <string name="le_mal"> Takumi et sa fille Hana vivent dans le village de Mizubiki, près de Tokyo. Comme leurs aînés avant eux, ils mènent une vie modeste en harmonie avec leur environnement. Le projet de construction d’un « camping glamour » dans le parc naturel voisin, offrant aux citadins une échappatoire tout confort vers la nature, va mettre en danger l’équilibre écologique du site et affecter profondément la vie de Takumi et des villageois…</string>
    <string name="john_wick">  Super-assassin John Wick (Keanu Reeves) returns with a $14M price tag on his head and an army of bounty-hunting killers on his trail. After killing a member of the shadowy international assassin’s guild, the High Table, John Wick is ex-communicado, but the world’s most ruthless hit men and women await his every turn.</string>
    <string name="le_comte">  Victime d’un complot, le jeune Edmond Dantès est arrêté le jour de son marriage pour un crime qu’il n’a pas commis. Après quatorze ans de détention au château d’If, il parvient à s’évader. Devenu immensément riche, il revient sous l’identité du comte de Monte-Cristo pour se venger des trois hommes qui l’ont trahi.</string>


</resources>